Benjamin H. Wolf Papers 5305
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- David Bogen Co., Inc. vs. Local B-1010, Radio Union, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), 7/23/52, 1952 (Box 1.1, Folder 17)
  Decision - Vacation pay
- Bertha Wendroff vs. Local 377, United Service Employees, 7/23/52, 1952 (Box 1.1, Folder 18)
  Decision - Schedules of work, welfare fund
- Cushman's Sons, Inc. vs. Local 50, American Bakery & Confectionery Workers Union (ABCWU), 9/4/52., 1952 (Box 1.1, Folder 19)
  Decision - Premium Pay
- Y & S Upholstery Co. vs. Local 224, Amalgamated Union, 11/9/52. (Box 1.1, Folder 20)
  Decision - Contract negotiations
- Simton Drug Co., Inc. vs. Allied Trades Council, 5/11/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 21)
  Decision - Discharge, Negligence & Carelessness, Dishonesty
- Chain Bike Corporation vs. United Construction Workers, United Mine Workers of America (UMW), 5/14/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 22)
  Decision - Discharge, Insubordination
- Guild Industries, Inc. vs. Local 76B, Furniture Workers of America, (UFW), 5/20/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 23)
  Decision - Interpretation of Past Arbitration Award, Rates of pay
- Jaeton Novelty, Inc. vs. Local 130, Amalgamated Workers Union, 6/1/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 24)
- Samuel Sumars d/b/a/ Steel Fabrication Co. vs. Local 455, International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers (IABSOIW), 6/5/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 25)
  Decision - Discharge, transfer
- Forest Box & Lumber Co., Inc. vs. Local 205 Lumber Plants & Allied Products, 6/5/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 26)
- Farchester Gardens vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 6/25/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 27)
  Decision - Rates of pay, Vacation
- Hewitt-Robbins, Inc. vs. Locals 30, 30A, International Union of Operating Engineers (IUOE), 6/30/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 28)
  Decision - Jurisdiction (Classification of jobs)
- Regent Quality Furniture, Inc. Fineman Furniture Co., Inc., Al Fineman, d/b/a/ Corvell Furniture Salesrooms Co. vs. Local 853, Retail Furniture & Floor Covering Employees Union, 7/16/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 29)
  Decision - Strikes, Contract Interpretation
- Beachview Lumber Co. vs. District 65, DPOWA, 7/30/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 30)
- Cabinet Craftsmen, Inc. vs. Local 76B, UFW, 8/12/53., 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 31)
  Decision - Layoff, Vacation pay
- Gates Lumber Co., Inc. vs. District 65, DPOWA, 8/19/53 (Box 1.1, Folder 32)
- Bell Custom & Upholstery Supply Inc. vs. Local 76, Upholsterers & Springmakers Union, UFW, 9/1/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 33)
  Decision - Holiday pay, Vacation pay
- General Bronze Corporation vs. Local 66, Architectural & Engineering Guild, American Federation of Technical Engineers, 9/14/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 34)
  Decision - Holiday pay
- Peter Ugarte vs. Local 813, IBT, 9/21/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 35)
  Decision - Pension fund
- Morey Machinery Co., Inc. vs. Local 1199, RWDSU, 9/23/53., 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 36)
  Decision - pension fund, welfare fund
- Stapleton Drug Co., Inc. vs. Local 1199, RWDSU, 9/23/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 37)
  Decision - Pension Fund, Welfare Fund
- Novelty Belts Manufacturing Co., Inc. vs. Local 35, Leather Workers of Greater NY, 9/23/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 38)
- S.B. Thomas, Inc. vs. Local 50, ABCWU, 10/7/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 39)
  Decision - Discharge, Absence
- S.B. Thomas, Inc. vs. Local 50, ABCWU, 10/15/53., 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 40)
  Decision - Discharge, Alcoholism, Discrimination
- Henry Heide, Inc. vs. Local 50, Candy & Confectionery Workers Union, 10/23/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 41)
  Decision - Discharge, Retirement, Incompetence, Inefficiency
- Walter Balfour and Co., Inc., vs. Local 455, IABSOIW, 11/6/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 42)
  Decision - Discharge, Improper job attitude
- Pathe Tool Mfg. Co., Inc., vs. Local 463, International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (IUE), 11/25/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 43)
  Decision - Discharge, Discrimination
- Rolo Realty Co., vs. Local 377, United Service Employees, 11/17/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 44)
  Decision - Discharge, Carelessness
- 150 William Street Corporation vs. Local 670, Peter Clinton, Stationery Engineers, 11/13/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 45)
  Decision - Discharge, Leaving Work Area without Permission
- Jay Kay Metal Specialties Corporation vs. Local 377, United Service Employees Union 11/16/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 46)
  Decision - Discharge, Leaving Work Area Without Permission
- Perlin Decorators, Inc. vs. Local 76, UFW, 12/1/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 47)
  Decision - Reduction in Force
- Morey Machinery Co., Inc. vs. Local 1227, UE, 12/8/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 48)
  Decision - Promotion
- Hotel Bedding & Upholstery Corporation vs. Local 140, UFW, 12/8/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 49)
  Decision - Rates of Pay, Pension Plan
- Long Island University vs. Local 32-K, BSEIU, 12/15/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 50)
  Decision - Rates of Pay, Workweek
- Greer Hydraulics, Inc. vs. Local 365, United Automobile Workers of America (UAW), 12/28/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 51)
  Decision - Discharge, Falsification
- Singer Cabinet Shops, Inc. vs. Local 76B, UFW, 12/30/53, 1953 (Box 1.1, Folder 52)
  Decision - Holiday pay.
- Lutheran medical Center vs. Local 1199, RWDSU, 12/1/64, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Decision - Arbitrability, Past Practice, Compensation
- R.H. Macy & Co., Inc. vs. Local 1-S, RWDSU, 12/2/64, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Decision - Discipline, Burden of Proof
- Brooklyn Union Gas Co. vs. Local 101, TWU, 12/10/64, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Decision - Arbitrability, Past practice, Lunch Periods, Rates of Pay, Schedules of Work
- Buttercup Farms, Inc. vs. Local 584, Milk Drivers and Dairy Employees, 12/21/64, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Decision - Discharge Burden of Proof
- Willette Corp. vs. Local 1336, TWUA, 12/28/64, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Decision - Discharge, Burden of Proof, Termination of Employment, Medical Release
- Finch, Pruyn & Co., Inc. vs. IBPSPMW, 1/8/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Decision - Discharge, Burden of Proof, Insubordination Remedies
- Jewish Home & Hospital for Aged vs. Local 1199, RWDSU, 1/8/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Decision - Discharge, Absences, Tardiness, Improper Personal Conduct
- Meldisco Corp. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 1/26/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Decision - Discharge, Gambling, Plant Rules
- Railway Express Agency vs. Local 808, IBT, 1/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Decision - Assignment of Jobs, Duty to Bargain
- Nyal Co., Inc. vs. Local 815, IBT, 2/9/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Decision - Rates of Pay
- Research Cottrel, Inc. vs. Local 443, International Chemical Workers Union (ICWU), 2/23/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Decision - Suspension, Discipline, Insubordination, Improper Personal Behavior, Overtime
- Packaging Industries Limited, Inc. vs. Local 427, IUE, 3/1/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  Decision - Discharge, Burden of Proof, Standards of Production, Incompetence and Inefficiency
- Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. vs. Local 464, Amalgamated Meat Cutters, 3/4/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Decision - Discharge, Burden of Proof, Alcoholism, Drinking and Intoxication
- Louis Lanza, d/b/a Lanza Donut Shop vs. Local 150, RCIA, 3/16/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Decision - Employer-Union Relations, Contractual Duty
- Schnefel Brothers Corp. vs. Local 2636, USA, 3/25/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Decision - Seniority, Recall
- Eastern Freightways, Inc. vs. Local 560, IBT, 3/29/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Decision - Discharge, Alcoholism, Drinking and Intoxication, Improper Personal Conduct
- Alderson Research Laboratories, Inc. vs. District 15, IAM, 4/20/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Decision - Contract Interpretation, Sick Leave and Sick Pay
- Westchester Square Hospital vs. Local 144, BSEIU, 4/20/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Medical Arts Hospital vs. Local 144, BSEIU, 4/26/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Decision - Dress, Contract Interpretation
- Bader Industries, Inc. (American Aquarium Co.) vs. Local 569, Sheet Metal Workers, 5/27/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Decision - Rate of Pay
- Tenaco, Div. of Coca-Cola vs. Local 478, IBT, 6/2/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Decision - Classification of Jobs, Rates of Pay
- Great Bay Chemicals & Plastics, Inc. vs. Local 8-716, OCAWIU, 6/7/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Decision - Timeliness, Classification of Jobs, Rates of Pay
- JFD Electronics Corp. vs. Local 584, IBT, 6/7/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  Decision - Management Rights, Schedules of Work
- A.T. Dodge Co., Inc. vs. Locals 15, 27, 35 of New Jersey, Bricklayers, Masons & Plasterers International Union of America, Executive Committee of Middlesex County, 6/15/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  Decision - Hiring
- Dorman Mills vs. TWUA, 6/18/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  Decision - Contract Interpretation, Rates of Pay, Evaluation of Job Factors
- Atlantis Publishing Co. vs. Newspaper Guild of NY, 6/22/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  Decision - Evaluation of Job Factors, Union Security
- Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. vs. Local 1212, IBEW, 6/22/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  Decision - Vacation, Schedules of
- John Engelhorn & Sons vs. Local 478, IBT, 6/25/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  Decision - Discharge, Burden of Proof, Theft, Falsification
- Eastern Colortype Co. vs. Local 62, International Brotherhood of Bookbinders, 7/26/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  Decision - Contract Interpretation, Evaluation of Job Factors, Jurisdiction
- Rex Shoe Co. vs. District 50, UMWA, 7/27/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  Decision - Discipline, Back Pay Awards, Contract Interpretation
- Associated Transport, Inc. vs. Local 707, IBT, 7/29/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Kings Highway Medical Group vs. Local 1199, RWDSU, 7/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  Decision - Arbitrability, Past Practice, Back Pay Awards
- A. Goodman & Sons, Inc. vs. Local 269, BCW, 8/18/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  Decision - Bonuses, Past Practices, Rates of Pay
- Home News Publishing Co. vs. Local 11, Newark Mailers Union, 8/23/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  Decision - Jurisdiction, Evaluation of Job Factors
- Associated Transport Co. vs. Local 478, IBT, 8/30/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  Decision - Discharge, Incompetence & Inefficiency, Theft
- Purlator Products, Inc. vs. Local 32, Office Employees' International Union, 8/30/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  Decision - Evaluation of Job Factors, Classification of Jobs
- Detecto Scales, Inc. vs. Local 810, IBT, 9/21/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Kings Highway Medical Group vs. Local 1199, RWDSU, 10/4/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  Decision - Arbitrability, Rates of Pay, Overtime, Workweek
- Charles Schwartz, d/b/a Four Aces Bar & Grill vs. Local 15, Bartenders Union of NYC, 10/4/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  Decision - Contractual Duties, Welfare Fund
- Flushing Hospital vs. Local 1199, RWDSU, 10/8/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  Decision - Arbitrability, Classification of Jobs, Evaluation of Job Factors
- Motts Cove Restaurant Inc. d/b/a Swan Club vs. Local 923, RWDSU, 10/27/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  Decision - Arbitrability, Contractual Obligations
- Brooklyn Union Gas Co. vs. Local 101, Utility Div., TWUA, 10/28/65, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  Decision - Discharge, Burden of Proof, Ability, Bumping, Back Pay Awards
- Greater N.Y. Plumbing and Heating Employees Association vs. Local 282, IBT, 1/6/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 1)
  Decision - Rates of Pay, Welfare Plan
- Plumbing and Heating Wholesale Association vs. Local 282, IBT, 1/6/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 2)
- Starr Parlor Frame Co., Inc., Local 76B, UFW, 1/7/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 3)
- Lazar Rappaport d/b/a Rappaport's Fish market and Bronx & Manhattan Retail Fish Dealers Association, Inc. vs. Local 635, Fish Workers Union, 1/8/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 4)
  Decision - Discharge, Workweek
- North Brooklyn Supply Co. vs. Local 140, UFW, 1/18/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 5)
  Decision - Vacation pay, Successor company
- Richardson & Dutt Inc. vs. Local 282, IBT, 2/1/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 6)
  Decision - Discharge, Improper Job Attitude
- Apex Brass & Bronze Works, Inc. vs. Local 455, IABSOIW, 2/8/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 7)
  Decision - Layoff, Seniority
- Steel Scaffolding Co., Inc. vs. Local 455, IABSOIW, 2/9/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 8)
- The Steel Scaffolding Co., Inc. vs. Local 455, IABSOIW, 2/9/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 9)
  Decision - Classification of jobs
- Grodnick Textile Co. vs. District 65, DPOWA, 2/23/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 10)
  Decision - Classification of Jobs
- Sam Roth vs. Local 670, RWDSU, 3/10/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 11)
  Decision - Discharge, Sick Leave, Absences
- Wee Moderns, Inc. vs. Local 169, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (ACWA), 3/11/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 12)
  Decision - Discharge, Work Stoppages, Rates of Pay
- S & S Sheet Metal Works vs. Local 222, Industrial Production Workers Union, 3/18/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 13)
  Decision - Welfare Funds
- Style Metal Specialists vs. Local 147, Watch and Jewelry Workers Union, 3/19/54 (Box 2.1, Folder 14)
  Decision - Discharge - Fights and Altercations
- William Stern, Stern Decorators vs. Local 76, UFW, 3/30/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 15)
  Decision - Vacation pay, back pay
- Superior Arm Co., vs. District 65, DPOWA, 4/1/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 16)
  Decision - Contract Negotiations, Holidays, Vacation, Rates of Pay, Medical Insurance
- Tri-State Associated Telephone Co. vs. Local 1566-1, IBEW, 4/1/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 17)
- Superior Arm Co., vs. District 65, DPOWA, 4/1/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 18)
- Holmes Private Ambulance Service vs. Local 643, IBT, 4/2/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 19)
  Decision - Workweek, Duration of Agreement, Holidays
- Berke-Ressler Co., Inc. vs. Local 76, UFW, 4/8/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 20)
  Decision - Part-time Employee
- Abbott Office and Window Cleaning Office vs. Local 32-J, BSEIU, 4/8/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 21)
- Steel Scaffolding Co., Inc. vs. Local 455, IABSOIW, 4/8/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 22)
  Decision - Discharge, Absences, Classification of Jobs.
- Eli L. Hirechorn d/b/a Hershey Furniture Co. vs. Local 853, UFW, 4/9/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 23)
  Decision - Compensation
- New York Rubber Corporation vs. Local 23453, Rubber Workers' Federal Labor Union, 4/29/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 24)
  Decision - Issue Withdrawn
- Lazar Rapaport vs. Local 635, Fish Workers Union, 5/3/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 25)
  Decision - Workweek
- Acme Concrete Burial Vault Co., Seal Lock Burial Vault Co., Inc. and American and Norwalk Vault Co. vs. Local 643 IBT, 5/12/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 26)
  Decision - Contract Negotiations
- Steel Scaffolding Co., Inc. vs. Local 455, IABSOIW, 5/14/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 27)
  Decision - Discharge, Absences, Vacation, Severance pay
- Lincoln School of Radio and Television vs. Local 2, American Federation of Teachers (AFT), 5/20/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 28)
  Decision - Discipline, Absence
- Steel Scaffolding Co., Inc. vs. Local 455, IABSOIW, 6/1/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 29)
- Berke-Ressler Co., Inc. vs. Local 76, UFW, 6/9/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 30)
  Decision - Job Description, Vacation, Holiday Pay, Rates of Pay
- Adams Refrigeration Service Corp., Bart Refrigeration Co., Inc. and Others vs. Local 1, Refrigeration, Air Conditioning, Appliances, Installation, Service and Production Employees' Union, 6/11/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 31)
- Terminal Barber Shops, Inc. vs. Terminal Barbers' Guild, 6/18/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 32)
  Decision - Holiday Pay
- M.N. Axinn Co. vs. Local 1205, IBT, 6/24/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 33)
  Decision - Rates of pay
- Eldred Manufacturing Co. vs. Local 670, Engineers, Firemen, maintenance and Building Service Union, 6/25/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 34)
  Decision - Discharge, Fights & Altercations, Negligence and Carelessness
- Plastic Heat Sealers Co., Inc. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 6/28/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 35)
  Decision - Discharge, Dishonesty
- Roanwell Corporation vs. Local 463, IUE, 7/1/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 36)
- Hotel Bedding Corporation vs. Local 140, UFW, 7/9/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 37)
  Decision - Holiday Pay.
- Park Surgical Co., Inc. vs. Local 1199, RWDSU. 7/12/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 38)
  Decision - Elimination of Jobs
- Fink Baking Corp., vs. Local 1, Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union, (BCW), 7/13/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 39)
  Decision - Contract Interpretation, Holiday Pay
- General Baking Co. vs. Local 550, IBT, 7/21/54., 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 40)
  Decision - Discharge, Probationary period.
- National Motor Rebuilding Corp., District 15, IAM, 7/29/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 41)
  Decision - Welfare Funds, Vacation Pay
- Montauk Iron and Steel Corp. vs. Local 815, IBT, 8/30/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 42)
- Arbuck, Inc. vs. Local 475, UE, 9/8/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 43)
  Decision - Discharge, Theft
- Novelty Belt Mfg. Co. vs. Local 35, Leather Workers of Greater New York, 9/8/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 44)
  Decision - Discharge
- Tyler Made Co., Inc. vs. Local 169, Washable Clothing, Sportswear and Novelty Workers, 9/22/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 45)
  Decision - Financial Responsibility
- K. Polishook and Son Corporation vs. Local 1, International Jewelry Workers Union, 9/22/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 46)
- Monarch Metal Producers vs. Local 400, Sheet Metal Workers International Association, 10/5/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 47)
- Kay Manufacturing Corp., vs. Local 76, UFW, 10/26/54., 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 48)
  Decision - Vacation Pay, Management Rights, Absences, Classification of Jobs
- Wilrose Specialty Store vs. Harlem Labor Union, 11/1/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 49)
  Decision - Holidays, Holiday pay, Crew size
- Napco Corporation vs. Local 1614, IBEW, 11/5/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 50)
- Shamus Culhane Production, Inc., Local 841, IATSE, 11/12/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 51)
  Decision - Lay-off, Vacation Pay, Severance Pay
- Wucker Furniture Co. vs. Local 853, UFW, 12/9/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 52)
- Steel Scaffolding Co. vs. Local 455, IABSOIW, 12/13/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 53)
  Decision - Suspension, Carelessness, Time Study, Standards of Production
- Ed Downer Lumber Corp., Local 1205, IBT, 12/29/54, 1954 (Box 2.1, Folder 54)
  Decision - Contract Interpretation, Refusal to Pay
- Livingston Sales, Inc. vs. Local 138, IBT, 1/7/55, 1955 (Box 2.1, Folder 55)
- Fisher Scientific Co., vs. District 50, UMW, 1/11/55, 1955 (Box 2.1, Folder 56)
  Decision - Holidays
- Duralin Process Shoe Service vs. Local 563, RWDSU, 1/17/55, 1955 (Box 2.1, Folder 57)
  Decision - Holiday Pay, Welfare Fund
- JFD Manufacturing Co., vs. Local 834, IBT, 2/9/55, 1955 (Box 2.1, Folder 58)
  Decision - Dismissal, Fights & Altercations, Suspension, Absences
- Voco Inc. and/or Voco Distributors, Inc. vs. Local 1614, IBEW, 3/1/55, 1955 (Box 2.1, Folder 59)
- Peerless Blueprint Co. vs. Local 24910, Blueprint, Photostat and Photo Employees Union, 3/10/55, 1955 (Box 2.1, Folder 60)
  Decision - Rates of Pay, Vacation
- I. Fenster and Sons, Inc., N.Y. Mounters Association, Inc. vs. Local 107, International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers (IBPSPMW), 3/14/55, 1955 (Box 2.1, Folder 61)
- Steel Scaffolding Co. vs. Local 455, IABSOIW, 3/28/55, 1955 (Box 2.1, Folder 62)
  Decision - Standards of Production
- Coil Winders Inc., vs. Local 463, IUE, 3/29/55, 1955 (Box 2.1, Folder 63)
  Decision - Discipline, Absences
- Victoria Plating vs. Local 1146, Retail Clerks International Association, (RCIA), 3/30/55, 1955 (Box 2.1, Folder 64)
  Decision - Rates of Pay, Holidays
- Sonotone Corporation vs. Local 528, UE, 4/11/55, 1955 (Box 2.1, Folder 65)
  Decision - Reinstatement
- Thomas W. Dunn Co. vs. Local 853, IBT, 11/5/65, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Decision - Reinstatement, Leaves of Absence, Contractual Duties
- U.S. Dredging Corp. vs. Local 136, 136B, IUOE, 11/24/65, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Decision - Classification of Jobs, Evaluation of Job Factors
- Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. vs. Local 1212, IBEW, 11/26/65, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Decision - Evaluation of Job Factors
- Plaza Barber Shops vs. Local 760, Journeymen Barbers International Union, 12/2/65, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Decision - Contract Modification, Rates of Pay
- Public Service Electric & Gas Co. vs. Utility Coworkers' Association, 12/6/65, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Decision - Jurisdiction, Assignment of Jobs
- Zenith Radio Corp. vs. Independent Radionic Workers of America, 12/17/65, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Decision - Discharge, Contractual Duties
- Tenco, Div. of Coca Cola Co. vs. Local 478, IBT, 12/24/65, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Decision - Rates of Pay, Classification of Jobs
- Jaynes Motor Freight vs. Local 478, IBT, 12/30/65, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Decision - Discharge, Insubordination, Management Rights
- Paterson Caterers vs. Local 158, Bartenders, 12/30/65, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Decision - Discharge, Alcoholism, Drinking, Intoxication, Remedies, Assignment of Jobs, Contract Interpretation
- Educational Broadcasting Co. vs. Local 1212, IBEW, 2/7/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Strahs Aluminum vs. District 65, RWDSU, 2/17/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Decision - Arbitrability, Discharge, Burden of Proof, Past Practice, Alcoholism, Drinking & Intoxication
- Middleton Card Co. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 2/23/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Decision - Discharge, Absenteeism, Tardiness
- Cosmos Industries, Inc. vs. Local 815, IBT, 2/26/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Century Transit Mix vs. Local 282, IBT, 2/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Decision - Sale of Business, Discharge, Burden of Proof
- H.W. Taynton Co., Inc. vs. Local 707, Highway and Local Motor Freight Drivers, Dockmen and Helpers, 3/7/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Decision - Assignment of Jobs, Ability, Dishonesty
- Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co. vs. Local 343, Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Retail Food Store Employees Union, 3/24/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Heil Co. vs. Local 574, UAW, 3/30/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Decision - Duty to Bargain, Schedules of Work, Assignment of Jobs, Overtime
- Lithographer & Photoengravers International Union vs. Local 153, Office Employees International Union, 3/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Decision - Past Practice, Working Conditions, Duty to Bargain, Inter-Union Disputes
- Rounder's Restaurant vs. Local 158, Bartenders, 4/4/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Associated Transport Inc. vs. Local 707, Highway & Local Motor Freight Drivers, Dockmen and Helpers, 4/5/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Decision - Discharge, Insubordination, Remedies
- Howard Fuel Co. vs. Local 553, IBT, 4/11/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Dairymen's League Cooperative Assn., Inc. vs. Local 584, IBT, 4/13/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  Decision - Discharge, Dishonesty, Falsification, Burden of Proof
- Enos Cozier vs. Local 6, Hotel and Club Employees Union, 4/18/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  Decision - Intra-Union Disputes, Hiring, Hiring Hall
- R.H. Macy & Co., Inc. vs. Local 1-S, RWDSU, 4/28/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  Decision - Arbitrability, Classification of Jobs
- Empty (Box 3, Folder 25)
  Decisions concerning Brooklyn Union Gas Co. & Local 101, TWA after 5/13/66 are filed separately at the end of the collection
- Roman's Mail Order, Inc. vs. District, RWDSU, 5/19/66 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  Decision - Classification of Jobs, Rates of Pay, Red Circle Rates
- Toms River Chemical Corp. vs. Local 140, NFIU, 5/31/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  Decision - Schedules of Work, Shift Scheduling, Demotions, Insubordination, Reinstatement
- Hi-Torc Motor Corp. vs. Local 431, IUE, 6/7/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  Decision - Discharge, Improper Personal Conduct, Insubordination
- H.L. Bishop, Inc. vs. Local 282, IBT, 6/15/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Empty (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Estate of James Sloan, Deceased vs. Milk Industry, Drivers & Dairy Employees Unions Pension Fund, 6/20/66, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  Decision - Employees' Rights